

CONTACT

- daniellechiefe3@gmail.com
- +639053743240
- Rizal, Philippines

SKILLS

- Strategic brand and influencer management.
- Expert in coordinating market approaches to make the brand stand out.
- Expert in sourcing influencers/content creators who align with the brands content or niche.
- Attention to detail for precise analysis of data.
- Strong time management skills and ability to meet deadlines Creative and has a good problem solving skills

DANIELLE CHIEFE

Influencer Marketing Specialist

An influencer marketing expert with outstanding project management skills and strategic mindset in achieving campaign goals and deadlines. A resourceful person that has an impeccable verbal and communication skills, with over one year of experience in influencer marketing.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CHALKOLA

Influencer Lead

May 2022- Jan 2024

Developed a content and social media strategy to increase rankings to Top 3. In the first 3 months we increased sales over 300%

Fostered relationship with social media influencers to amplify content reach.

Manage brands to all the elements of any other job resume but showcases the skills and experience unique to SEO specialists

INBEAT AGENCY

May 2022- July 2023

Campaign Manager

Managed the development of paid media, campaign flighting, budgets and all aspects of campaign development

- Tracked and reported metrics for all online and print lead generation Worked closely with Customer Insights, and Experience, Loyalty
- Marketing Marketing and Social Media, direct response emails.

DIGITAL STARK

July 2021 - May 2022

Team Leader & Project Manager

Team Leader and Project Manager in Malaysia and Philippines handling teams, and creating successful influencer marketing projects.

Supervise the team responsible for promoting products and services and establishes goals and initiatives to find new markets.

Expert in research influencers based on category, industry experts, competitors, target audience and users

Report & track project performance in all our platforms according to the internal company's KPI

FREELANCE INFLUENCER DISCOVERY

Influencer Marketing Specialist

July 2022-Nov 2022

Source influencers/content creators who align with the brands content

Connect to influencers with the rate and coordinate project details and deadlines...

ISLAND GETAWAY TRAVEL AND TOURS Nov 2017-

Social Media Marketer

Feb 2018

Execute social media strategy through competitive research, platform determination, benchmarking,

Creates and distribute engaging written content in the company's social media page.

EDUCATION

OUR LADY OF FATIMA UNIVERSITY

2018-2022

Bachelor of Science in Psychology
HANBAT NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

2020-2021

Major in English and Literature